

# Tanveer Najib

I am a reliable, enthusiastic and dedicated individual with the ability to adapt in any given task. I am an effective communicator who is able to organise a group in a workplace while keeping efficient in my own given task. I am a person who is always doing a job to the best of my ability, and I always aim to achieve a perfect result. I have been highly successful in meeting targets and have a driven work ethic. I am always ready to learn new skills and I have proven track records of attendance and punctuality. My previous experiences have improved my skills in computing and have given me a passion for working in a computer-based environment.

### Hobbies & Interests

- Socialising with my family and friends
- Meeting new people
- Programming
- Graphics Design
- Contributing to Open Source projects
- Reading comics/books

### Links



- tanveernajib@qmail.com



https://crxssed.dev

- https://github.com/crxssed7

in

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/ tanveer-najib/

## Work Experience

#### Junior Software Developer @ GWD

September 2021 - March 2022

Part of the 6 month long kickstart scheme. Spearheaded the development of multiple internal projects and worked with different departments. I worked on a company statistics portal alongside upper management to ensure the best implementation.

#### Software Engineer @ Weightron Bilanciai September 2020 - July 2021

Started as first-line support, eventually moving on to developing systems for clients, as well as supporting them. Learnt the in-house programming language that is used for customer systems within one month. During the 11 months I learnt more about MSSQL and how to integrate it as a backend.

### Education

QA Software Bootcamp

August 2022 - present

- Microsoft Azure AZ-900: PASS

#### Meadowhead School

September 2018 - July 2020 (A LEVEL)

- Computer Science: B - English Language: B

- History: C

September 2012 - July 2018 (GCSE)

- Combined Science: 6/5 - English Language: 6

- History: 6

- Computer Science: 5 - Religious Studies: 5

- Maths: **5** 

- English Literature: 4

## Technical Skills

- C#
- Python
- JavaScript
- Flutter
- 00P
- Git
- Agile

Help me expand this list!